My name is Yasmin .
I 'm three months pregnant .
According to the constitution , everyone is created equal .
But this is not what happens in my world .
I don 't want to bring my baby into a world full of prejudice and hatred !
I decided to protect my baby from this type of environment .
FRONTIER
It ' my choice ...
On the second round of the Presidential elections ...
The crowd 's anger ...
and the action by the police ...
set off the riots ...
against the right wing political party .
And the situation keeps deteriorating ...
We 're almost there , come on !
Easy ... easy !
Stop ! Freeze !
Just a couple more steps .
- Easy , ohh ... - OK .
Stop !
Alex , don 't do anything stupid !
- What the hell you 're doing , Alex ? - Stop !
- Hold it right there ! - Alex , stop , for Christ sake !
Now what , pig ? Don 't you move !
I should fucking kill you . You 're not so fucking tough now , are you ? Huh ?
You fucking Pig !
- Fuck him Alex , we got to get out of here ! - Come on , man . Let 's go !
- Alex , let 's get the fuck otta here ! Now ! - Let 's go , man , hurry up !
- Yeah ? - Sami got shot , and he 's losing a lot of blood !
- Where are you guys ? - Oh , shit !
- Your brother got shot , and he 's hurt bad ! - You gotta get him to a hospital !
No , no , no , no hold on , Yasmin ! Wait till we get there , don 't do anything , just wait , Ok ?
I can 't just sit here , watch him bleed to death and do nothing , Alex .
Didn 't you hear me ? Yas ! I told you to stay put , damn it !
- That 's stupid , man , my brother 's hurt ! - That 's not our fault , is it ?
Nobody forced him to get involved .
- I guess we just go our own way . - What about me and Yas ?
- She wants nothing to do you , I guess you know why . - Yas , is still my woman !
Come on , let 's get going !
- Farid stop , I 'm not in the mood , ok . - Something for us to remember .
- Well , we finely made it . - Where you guys been ?
- What took you so long ? - The cops are all over , and roadblocks everywhere .
- We gotta get out of the city . - He can 't travel like this .
- That 's taking too much of a chance . - Hey , you 're talking about my brother .
- It 's all your fault ! - My fault , huh ? I didn 't twist his arm to come along .
- You 're such a damn fool ! - Everybody just calm down !
Look , we gotta figure out , what we gonna do here , okay ?
- I 'm gonna take him to the hospital ! - The city is full of cops , you can 't do it alone , okay
He is right , let me figure something out .
- It 's not for you to decide . - Shut the fuck up !
You 're a dumb son of a bitch .
Tom , we got to get him to a doctor .
Ok , here is what we gonna do ...
You and Farid take one car drive up to the border and check in a motel .
Yas and I , take the other car , get him to the hospital , and we meet at the motel later .
- Alright ? - Okay .
Okay .
I rather die , then go with this idiot !
You 're fucking crazy ! I 'm just trying to help , huh ?
- Please , Farid please , take me with you . - You got to get to a hospital .
I don 't wanna stay here by myself .
What the hell , do you want ?
- How you feeling ? - I 've been better .
What about our baby ?
All of a sudden you 're interested ? Who you 're kidding .
- I 'll take care of it myself . - Yas ?
I 'm gonna get an abortion , so you won 't have to worry any more .
- Yas , don 't do this because of me . - I 'm doing it for me .
Farid , you idiot , turn the fucking alarm off ! You want the cops to know we 're here ?
Sorry I 'll keep it down .
- How much we got ? - 112,500 ...
plus some more here and here .
- You know it belongs to everybody , right ? - There 's plenty for everybody .
- When 're we gonna split the money ? - Why 'd you wanna know now ?
- I just wanna know when , that 's all , - I 'm not dead yet , you son of a bitch !
- Look , I trust him , he always keeps his word . - Get in the car !
Okay , if we leave now , boss ? Are they worried , about me taking off with the money ?
Alright , we are going , bye .
Good luck , Sami .
The authorities have decided an a more severe punishment ...
for each occurring incident , also increasing reinforcements , all Suspect ...
will be detained at the military compound without bail , pending investigation .
Can 't wait to get out town , away from the fucking cops .
- Shut your mouth ! - Hurry up , and get him to the hospital , ok ?
Don 't touch me ! Don 't touch me !
- Can 't you drive any faster ? - Shut up , I 'm doing my best ! We 're just about there , Ok !
Let get him up .
- Just her ! - You got him ?
Not you , son of a bitch ...
It 's gonna be fine .
Hold on , Sami , somebody 's right here .
- What happened ? - Please , get a doctor , help him , please .
- What happened ? - With all the chaos , they shot him , and he 's not even part of it .
- I 'll get the doctor . - Please , hurry .
I 'm going .
Yas ...
I 'll help you ...
With the baby , don 't abort it .
I don 't know , it 's hard ...
Being a single mother .
Screw him , he don 't have to be part of your life , it 's gonna be your child .
I love you , Sami .
I love you so much ...
I love you too , Yas ... you have to go .
They 're coming .
You got to go .
- I 'm not leaving you ! - You have to care of our share , it 's important .
I 'm not gonna let you be by yourself ! No , no ...
Go ...
Hello ! Ma 'am !
- Wait , I need to ask you a some questions . - Nooo ...
Stop , or you 're under arrest !
- Stop ! - No ...
- Are they helping him ? - Let 's go !
- What the fuck 's going on in there ? - Just drive !
Stop ! ... Shit !
Fuck , you almost got yourself caught , your brother is a damn weak-ass , you know he 's gonna squeal on us .
Sami is not gonna tell them anything . He just died , Alex !
Please , take me to my place , I wanna go home .
Please , Alex .
I 'm not gonna say anything , I promise .
You know , you can 't go back there , it would fuck up everything .
- I 'm beginning to relax . - Me too .
Well , we 're making good time .
Are we still in France ?
Yeah , we still got some ways to go .
Are there any other places besides where we 're going , in the country ?
Why ? Did you wanna stay in the city ?
Maybe .
I wanted to go to my father 's funeral with my brother .
But I got held up ...
I couldn 't get out of the district on time .
I promised myself then , once I get out of the district , I 'll never go back .
I got nobody waiting for me anyway .
Not even a girlfriend ?
Yeah right .
No , not even a girlfriend .
- Why 're we stopping ? - Shut up .
- What ? - Get out .
Why ?
Out !
- Sorry , the money stays in the car . - What ?
- Why you doing this ? - I told you to get out .
Get out of this fucking car , before I have to break your neck and drag you out , you hear me ?
Please stop , you 're hurting me ... stop , fooling around , please .
- That 's the last time I 'm gonna ask you to get out ! - Ok , I 'm getting out , I 'm going , okay ...
- Ok , okay I 'll get out . - Relax , man , I 'm just kidding .
We stop here and rest a while .
Idiot .
Don 't cry , be a man .
Did you get scared ?
Yea , I thought you were serious , ass-hole .
Hello ?
Tom , it 's me .
We 're on our way .
No , he 's okay , they said he 'll be fine .
- Where 're you at ? - Got about 3 more hours to go .
Ok , see you later .
Why didn 't you tell him the truth ?
There 's no reason to make it more complicated , you 're not alone in this , we 're all involved .
I 'm starting to feel really sick , I feel like throwing up .
I think I 'm gonna quit .
- Really ? - My mother will be happy to hear it .
She 'll think that I 've finely grown up .
- I need to get some sleep . - Me too .
- What 's that say ? - " Rooms " .
There 's always something free at these places .
Border
How wonder much they gonna charge ?
- Man , this is not Panama . - Right here , it 's perfect , Dude ...
Look , it 's out of the way .
Good evening , Ladies !
You have any rooms available ?
Yeah , we might have something .
- We have some rooms available . - Good , for one night .
- How many people ? - Two now .
Two more later .
- You two ? - Any others ... huh ?
Gentleman , fill out the register .
Goetz , we have customers !
- I can 't stand it . - Be quiet .
Hey , Goetz , where are you ?
Goetz !
What is it ?
Is number two ready ?
For how long ?
One night .
Ok , you guys can stay . Girls , take care of them .
Thanks .
- Like a drink ? - Yeah , that be great , thanks .
Nobody 's gonna believe , we ran in to this two beauties way out here .
You both are ... incredible .
You 're very charming , thanks .
What 's the matter with you , Dude ? This is fantastic ...
You guys , are very charming , and it 's a pleasure to have you here .
Who is the guy ? Is he somebody ¿ s husband ? He did say something about the room , or did he forget about us ?
No , no married couples here , I can tell , you 're very emotional and impulsive .
I guess he must be the boss then !
Farid , stop getting hung up , it seems the girls aren 't worried about him .
You 're right , Gilberte ... I am impulsive .
I 'm impulsive here ... and very , very much here .
Farid , are you afraid of us ?
No , no ... I have a girlfriend .
What 're doing ? You can 't stop now .
- Dude , we have a long drive tomorrow , all day ... - Enough with this nonsense ! Let 's have some fun .
Can we continue now ?
I can see you 're not getting bored .
At least you 're not pansy 's .
Gilberte ! ... take them to the room .
You can finish there .
- Let 's go to your room ? - Now ?
You said you wanted to finish . Claudia , take care of this one ...
We 'll have a good time together .
- Come , let 's go . - No , I have to call my girlfriend .
I promised her , I 'd call her tonight .
You don 't know what you 're missing .
Shit .
Fuck , Dude , they are sweet .
Come here , I 'm gonna fix you right up .
I am ready ...
Come on , come on , come on ...
Leave me alone , please , I have girlfriend !
Dude , come on , enjoy that sweet pussy !
- Let me go ! Please . - Come on , have some fun .
- I can 't , please don 't . - Come on , don 't be scared , act like a man !
- Something wrong ? - I 'm just surprised about the family get-together , so soon ...
It 's " hospitality " .
Pass your plates .
Thanks .
The food I prepare in my kitchen and serve you here ...
Builds up your strength and gives you energy .
Really !
Hmm 'mm ...
It 's delicious , what is it ?
It 's a pork roast .
You won 't get cold tonight .
It 's good for you , and it makes you firm .
Sorry , but I don 't eat pork , I not gonna eat it , sorry .
Are you a Jew ?
No , I 'm a Muslim , I just don 't like pork .
Girls give me a hand .
Claudia , open her mouth .
Leave me alone .
- Mom , you got to eat . - Come on !
Mom , open your mouth .
Stop wiggling , and swallow the food !
Stop playing games mom , if you don 't eat , we can 't help you ... did you hear , what I said ?
Swallow , the damn food . You 're starting to me pissed off , mom !
- Didn 't he like the food ? - What 's this ? I mean what 's going on ?
- You treat your mother like an animal . - We have to do this with mom , or she 'll starve ...
Okay , well , I seen enough .
- Are you tired ? - I don 't like your family get-togethers , they make me sick .
- Wait , ' till I get done helping dad . - What 's going on ?
You were right , Farid , they are damn whores .
No , no , I 'm sorry ... it was a joke .
He don 't know what he 's saying .
What 's the matter with you ? Are you drunk ?
Come to think of it , this whole thing is weird , she liked being spanked and kept asking for more .
I told you that they 're whores .
Everything just went to quick .
It just bothers me , because I liked her .
Shit , it 's Yas ...
Don 't say anything about this , she 'd kill me .
Hey !
Hey , we won 't be there for another two hours . How you guys doing ?
Pretty good here . How about you guys ?
Everything is just all messed up .
We had a problem at the hospital , Sami died .
I 'm so sorry .
- Where are you ? - We 're at a motel close by the border ...
I 'll send you the address by SMS .
- Don 't say anything to Farid yet . - I understand , I won 't .
See you later , take care .
Why you 're whispering ?
- Are you scared ? - Of what ? The people here ?
Fuck 'em .
Goddamn cunts .
Hey , so ...
What 'd you thinking ?
Nothing .
" News Bulletin "
The Minister of Interior is now officially the Candidate for the presidency of the Republic ,
He is also is the subject of the protests .
The instability of the country left a mark on the presidential campaign .
The police remains on maximum alert .
He 's a piece of shit !
I 'd like to strangle 'm with my bare hands .
All of them .
Country full of fucking fascists .
France and the USA ... run by right wing dictators .
What do you want ?
Me , nothing . Somebody wants to talk to you .
Good evening .
- Do you know why I 'm here ? - No , I don 't .
Where 're you guys from ?
From Paris .
Are you those guys , that have been rioting and burning cars ?
You gonna do the same thing here , huh ? What ? You guys got lost and ended up here ?
- We 're on our way to Holland ... - I 'm not talking to you , stupid !
Is that it ?
He 's telling you the truth , we 're on our way to Amsterdam , to see some friends .
Or ... you wanted to get laid .
So you went to look for some hookers , huh ?
And you came here ... thinking this was a whore-house ?
No , wait ... it 's not like that at all , we 're just two regular guys ...
- Do you think my sisters are whores ? - No , no ...
- Is that what you think they are ? - What ?
Do you ? Are you hard of hearing ?
Do you ? Answer me !
- Maybe ... - Huh ...
Hands up .
Hurry !
What did we do ?
- Gilberte said something about a bag of money . - She 's crazy .
Liar !
- It 's in here . - Gilberte , what 're you talking about ?
Those are our clothes , see for yourself ...
Goetz !
We got to get out of here , fast !
Tom !
Stop or I 'll shoot !
Enough ! Stop !
I told you enough !
- I 'll go get their luggage . - Stop !
Tom , my buddy .
Don 't move !
Goetz , you didn ¿ t kill him !
Get them !
Quick , get in the car !
They 're shooting at us !
He 's following us !
He 's coming after us !
Hurry , Tom , faster !
Come on , faster !
Step on it ! Burn some rubber !
Step on the gas ! Man !
He 's right beside us ! Get away from him !
Watch where you going !
- Now what ? - Turn left .
Well ?
They crashed into the canyon . Here , I got this .
Claudia !
Farid , come help me .
Farid , help me .
Farid , please , help get me out , easy ...
Here you go , easy , easy now ...
Careful , now .
Take it easy .
Shh , quiet .
Where are we ?
You alright ?
- Good evening . - Good evening .
Our relatives told us they were staying here .
Are you Tom and Farid 's Family ?
- Are they here ? - Not really , they went to another motel .
- Why didn 't they stay here ? - We have no vacancies .
What 's the name of the motel and how do we get there ?
Come on , follow me , I 'll show you , Claudia ! Stay here and wait for me .
Let 's go .
Why does she keep ordering me around ? I can 't stand it !
- Gilberte is the boss . - I 'm not her dog .
Have a little patients ! You 'll be taking her place soon !
Karl !
Goetz ! I put up the roadblocks .
Hurry up and get back here , father don 't like to be kept waiting .
Where are we ? Where 're we going ?
What 's that smell ? I can 't ... smells like a mortuary .
Hang on , ok ?
Maybe we should go back .
- Where to ? - To hell ?
- Let 's try to climb in there . - You wanna try first ?
Come on .
1,2,3 go ...
You Ok ?
What 's in there ?
I see some lights , up ahead !
I 'll get right behind you .
Hey what ? !
Go , come on .
- Come on . - Shit , I can 't breathe .
- I can 't ... - Come on .
I can 't breathe .
A little bit more !
Tom , we 're just about there .
Go on .
- Forget it , man , I 'm stuck . - We 're almost there .
- Stop telling me what to do . - The same goes for you .
- Tom try ! The lights are real close . - I told you I 'm stuck !
I 'm stuck , motherfucker !
Mom , where are you ?
Mom , I 'm dying ...
Mom !
Tom , only a little bit more , come on , go .
No !
Shit , are you a man or a fucking pussy ?
I 'm stuck !
Go , man , c 'mon ! One last effort !
I 'm fucking stuck , man !
Come on , Tom ! ... You just about got it ...
Come on !
Tom ...
Hurry !
Faster , for Christ sake !
Hurry ! ...
There 's somebody behind us !
Come on !
Fuck !
Ok , you made it , Tom .
- At the end of the road , turn right . - What is this ?
It 's an old mine , it 's been closed since the beginning of the century .
Hey , just relax . I 'm gonna go in and tell them you 're here .
No ! No !
Get away from me !
No !
Don 't pay any attention to her . She 's sick .
Good evening .
Sit down .
Thanks .
Claudia , boil some water .
The guns are for hunting . They organize hunting parties here .
Where 're you folks heading ?
To Holland , we 're going there on business .
Can I use your bathroom , please ?
Sure .
Come on , I 'll show you .
- Are you two married ? - No , we 're not together anymore .
It 's the door in the back .
Are you hungry ? Would you like something to drink ?
No , thank you .
Get in there !
Shut up !
He 's coming .
Claudia , help me .
- Who is coming ? - Father .
Sit up straight , he don 't like for people to slouch .
Greetings and welcome , lady traveler .
What 's your name ?
Yasmin .
Ihre hand .
Your hand .
Don 't stay here ...
Tom !
Get out now ...
Go now ...
You got to go now ...
- Get up . - What 's going on ?
- We 're leaving now ! - Why ? What happened ?
- Let 's get in the car now ! - What 's this ? Okay , that 's enough .
The killed our friend , Tom .
Alex ! Yas !
Karl !
Let 's get him on the grill and roast him medium well .
Listen , my son ...
The time has come , for us to renew the blood of our family .
But I do have some doubts about her .
I don 't know if she will be right for us .
Her complexion is too dark .
Her hair , her eyes ...
She is not of pure blood ,
But our choices are very limited .
You need a wife to take over my seat , as the Commander , we will make her your wife .
Remember we must continue our race .
My honor , must not be in doubt .
Eve , bleed him , then I 'll finish butchering him .
- What 's going on ? - I don 't know .
- There is somebody over in the storage room . - Huh ?
I 'm gonna go and see who it is ... I don 't like for anybody to mess with my meat .
Claudia , finish later , I 'm going with him .
Let 's pull !
Stop !
Hurry !
Shit .
Stop ! Stop !
You go check the engine room .
Where 're you hiding , creep ?
How you like this ? Creep , huh ?
You fucking son of a bitch !
I can 't leave you here alone , Alex .
Yas ...
You gatto go get help .
- Get help ! - No !
No !
Go !
Go get help !
Get help , and come back .
Hurry up !
Let 's go !
Just go !
Disgusting .
Open up !
Open the door ! Let me out !
Don 't stop , go !
Please go !
Hurry !
I love you .
Me too .
Go get help !
I 'm sorry , Alex .
Not now .
Please go .
Go now !
Don 't worry about me !
Please , Just go !
Please , hurry .
Good , you 're out , now go .
Bring back help .
Hurry , hurry .
Open the door !
Open the door ! Open the door !
Open ! ... Open ! ... Open ! ...
- Move over ! - Out of my way pigs .
Where is the girl ?
Go to hell , you fucking Nazi !
Did you hear this ? I will teach him a lesson ! Hurry ! ... and bring me the pliers .
Don 't ...
What 're you doing ?
I will take away your desire to escape , and make sure you will never walk again .
Get a hold of him .
Now ...
In Africa , the guards used this method on workers in the diamond mines ...
making sure they could never dream of going anyplace else again ...
I have to agree , the idea is marvelous , and it works great ... easy now ...
Easy now ...
Easy ... just about ...
I 'm Finished ! And through the all of the pain and their suffering ...
The people continued to work .
And Worked ! And Worked ! For their freedom , because ...
" Work Will Set You Free " !
Stop ! Please !
Please , help me ! Get me to a phone , I gotta call the police !
Yeah , hop in , lady .
You 're going the wrong way .
No , we 're fine , I 'm taking you home .
No !
- Shut your mouth ! - No ...
- Shut the door ! - No ...
- And keep it closed ! - No ...
- Shut up ! - No ...
Oh , no ...
Hans ! Come closer , my little boy ...
Yas !
Wonderful !
I will let you have one request !
One ... answer !
Just do it !
Fuck you and your father-land !
Get rid of him .
You did a fantastic job of annoying me .
Take him , Hans ! Be sure to preserve him .
Let 's finish cleaning her .
Are you pregnant ?
That 's great ...
Here , this will keep you warm .
You 'll be a member of the family soon .
You 're gonna get your own quiet room , for you to have the baby .
Is this okay ?
What do you think ?
I 've got something that can help you .
You and I are in the same boat ,
Father is happy because you 're also pregnant .
Drink this .
It makes things a little more bearable .
Drink .
This helps me when I give birth .
One more .
It 's strong , isn ¿ t it ?
Here drink .
- Another one . - No .
In your situation you have to be careful .
Beautiful hair .
But you have to cut it .
Father don 't like black hair .
Father says we are a unique breed .
They brought me here after the 2nd. world war .
They took me from my parents when I was little ...
But they promised me that my parents will come and see me , if I behaved .
Father wants all the girls here , to mature fast , so they can have babies .
All the kids born here , are deformed .
Father says the reason for that , is because of our blood , this will be my fourth baby .
Why don 't you leave this place ?
I 'm waiting for my parents to come , and visit me .
They promised me .
I know that they 'll come .
Parents just don 't abandoned their children .
I know what I 'm talking about .
I love children .
Father wanted to put all the deformed children in the gas chamber .
But Hans and I , we hid them , before he got a chance to do it .
They 're all living in the mine shafts , on the other side of the farm .
I go down and visit them , as much as I can .
I die if it wasn 't for them .
Let us welcome our guest .
Come in , sit down at our table .
Everybody take a seat .
Gentlemen , we are at the start of a new chapter , and we are there to write it .
To our new mother ,
who is now a member of our happy and wonderful family .
I am proud to announce the next happy event ... the expectance of a new arrival ...
If it is a girl she will be given the name Lilith .
If it is a boy he will be given the name Karl ... after his father .
Who will be joined in a bond of matrimony with our dearly beloved woman , Yasmin .
This is a year for great achievements , we have the opportunity and the stepping stone ...
to make our family more united and stronger , every day when you listen , you can hear ...
" The Wind Of Victory Blowing " .
At this time I like to announce my decision , of turning over the trust the care of our family ...
to my only son , Karl Von Geisler who makes me very proud .
Please stand up .
Thank you , father , This is a great honor .
From now on , you all will be responsible for your words , actions and loyalty ...
to your brother , my son , Karl .
You also must respect and help my beloved daughter , Gilberte .
This goes especially for you ,
Hans von Fracht .
I think you two were good friends at one time .
- You 're a sick old man . - You think so ? You need this more than I do .
Gilberte , my beloved daughter ,
Can you explain to this young lady , about her future , and what is expected of her , huh ?
So you understand , we will wait for you , dear lady , to give birth to the child .
This is a gesture of our concern .
Besides ... this is the only unborn member of our great race .
- No fucking way ! - What ?
You have to be nice to father , and show him respect .
You 're not gonna tell me what to do !
What a great way to show respect , to the authority of our new commander .
Goetz !
Karl !
Tell her to stand up .
Stand up !
And now ...
You will kiss each other , and the kiss is the seal ...
That will make our family her new and only family ,
So it will put an end to all the unnecessary disputes .
" Pure Blood " !
" Here is to pure Blood " !
Let me go !
- Let go of him ! - Let me go !
- Let go of him ! - Don 't come any closer or I 'll cut his throat !
Eve ! ... Open the door !
- Eve ! Don 't do it ! Eve ! - Drop the shotgun ...
Or I 'll make him bleed like a stuffed pig !
Hans , lower your gun ! That 's an order !
- Do it , Hans ! - Hans , you idiot ! Lower your weapon , that 's an order !
- Hans ! Lower your weapon . - Hans ! I am ordering you to lower your weapon , now !
- Lower your weapons , or I 'll cut him ! I swear ! - Hans , listen to her !
- These are not kid 's , so you better listen ! - I 'm not scared of you , fuck 's ! Neither one of you !
- Hans , don 't ! - This is an order ! Shoot that dog !
Nooo .
Don 't die , Hans !
Please , don 't , oh , no don 't .
Karl ! Let 's kill her !
Karl , over here !
- I 'll take the service road . - Meet me at the main entrance .
Fucking monsters .
I can sense you .
Come on out ,
Little bitch ...
You fucking cunt , where are you ?
Bitch , I know you ¿ re in here .
You want me to chop you up ?
You want me to kill you , huh ?
Come here !
Because you 're the wife of our commander , you don 't have to listen to me anymore , huh ?
And now you gonna tell me what to do , huh ?
Is that it ? is that what you think ?
You fucking cunt !
I 'm more important than you ! Me !
Right now I 'm the one calling the shots . Bitch !
Who picked you anyway ?
Here I 'm the boss ! huh ! Me , okay !
And you 'll do as I tell you !
And right now I 'm telling you , to get your ass over here !
Did you hear what the fuck I said ?
The whole thing was the old man 's idea ... Why should he decide who the fucking boss is ?
So let 's be clear about who the fucking boss is ! I 'm the boss !
I give the orders here ! You got that ?
Why did he appoint him ? Why did he choose him ? !
I 'm the boss , I give the orders ! So , you show me respect !
Look at me ! When I 'm talking to you , damn cunt ! Look at me !
You fucking whore !
Drop it ! You hear me ? Drop it , I said !
Good bye ...
I wanted to help ...
- Eve , you 're coming with me . - No .
- I can 't leave the kids . - Let 's get away from here .
They 're looking for you , I 'll tell them I haven 't seen you ... Go ! ... Hurry !
Claudia , she 's here !
Claudia ! ... Let 's stay together !
That 's enough !
Get out of here !
Is it over ?
It 's really over ?
- We 're not finished ! - No , don 't do this !
- Get out of the way ! - Don 't ! Don 't !
Eve , I said move !
- Don 't ! - I said move ! Idiot !
Get on your knees , bitch !
- Gilberte no ! - You 're dead !
- Come on , let 's go ! - No , my kids are here .
The disturbances related to the second round of the campaign ...
made the candidate of the extreme right wing , come to an agreement ...
after announcement of the results , the pressure was visible on his face .
The police is still in a state of high alert ...
Sorry , I don 't speak German .